https://www.realitymod.com/privacy

Privacy Statement
We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used at Project Reality's websites. We take extraordinary steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy.
Information Collection
Project Reality is the sole owner of the information collected from our website. We do not, or will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in our privacy statement below.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the visitor's hard drive containing information about the visitor. Advertisers connected to Project Reality at times require cookies to track statistics about products and locations, but at no time are these linked to any personal identification. At this time, Project Reality uses cookies only for login convenience.
Log Files
Project Reality keeps log files on broad fields to analyze trends, track user movements, and gather data for demographic locations. This is not attached in anyway to visitor's personal identification.
Sharing
At this time, Project Reality does not share any information with advertisers, merchants, or any other third party.
Links
Links to other sites outside of Project Reality do not apply to this privacy statement. We are not responsible for privacy policies of other websites linked to Project Reality. Please read the privacy statement of each website linked to Project Reality for information and data use for visitor's personal identification. Our privacy statement applies solely to Project Reality.
Contests
At any particular time, Project Reality will conduct contests for our visitor's. Visitor participation for these contests is voluntary, and in no way requires the visitor to give out personal information when choosing not to enter in the contest. Collected information may include contact information and demographic information, such as name, e-mail, address, state, ect. This information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes.
Changes of our Policy
This Privacy Statement is subject to change at anytime without notice. Please check this page frequently for changes.
Breaking the seat limit
Login server rework
Brecourt Assault historical layer explanation
Sangin - nearly ready for testing...
Copyright ©2004 - 2020, Project Reality.All Rights Reserved.
